Contact

6 october, giza 01113709072 (Mobile) redamahmoud722@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ mahmoud3899 (LinkedIn) github.com/MAHMOUDRR707 (Personal)

Top Skills

Leadership

Arduino

Electronics

Certifications

Convolutional Neural Networks HCIA-AI

Structuring Machine Learning Projects

Computer Vision Basics
Introduction to Internet of things

Mahmoud Reda

Machine Learning Engineer Cairo

Summary

Majoring in Computer Engineering, a technology and science enthusiast with the ability to learn rapidly and cooperate. Very flexible and willing to be pushed to the limits when it comes to working. Ex-intern at DevisonX as well as YAT both worked as a software engineer as Machine Learning Engineer and Mobile Android Developer.. Experienced in student activities as being a DSC founder, Member at IEEE ZSB CS and vice chairman at IEEE ZSB RAS.

Experience

Omdena
Junior Machine Learning Engineer
May 2021 - July 2021 (3 months)
Egypt

Spurwing Software Engineer Intern March 2021 - April 2021 (2 months) New York City Metropolitan Area

YAT

Android Developer Intern September 2020 - November 2020 (3 months) Cairo, Egypt

Working on Android Plant Diseases Application using Java, Flutter providing Al model to the application

Working on another sample projects mainly based on java

Start an introduction on UX.UI, HTML and CSS

DevisionX
Machine Learning Intern
September 2020 - November 2020 (3 months)
Cairo, Egypt

Machine Learning Engineer Internship specifically in Computer Vision Working on Building AutoAl tool such as AutoKeras, KerasTuner, and Optuna Build classification models and Object Detection models (with different formats like COCO,UDT , YOLO)

Deployment the models on the web

Build Script to convert between UDT format to COCO format

Education

Zagazig University

Bachelor's degree, Computer Engineering · (2017 - 2022)

Alsanawya elaskria High School Diploma · (2015 - 2017)